fasttrack.co.uk 2019-03-28

# Privacy & cookies policy - Fast Track

**Privacy policy** ** _  
_** Fast Track 100 Ltd (registered no 03323084) (“ **Fast Track** “, “ **we** “, “ **us** “, or “ **our** “) is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy, and complying with the obligations of a small company. This policy provides information pertinent to the processing of your personal data by us including when and why we collect personal data, how we use it and the conditions under which we may disclose it to third parties.

We are the “data controller” for the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998 and the “controller” for the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation when the GDPR comes into force on 25 May 2018.

Any questions regarding this policy can be sent in writing to Fast Track, 81 St Clement’s Street, Oxford, OX4 1AW; to [privacy@fasttrack.co.uk](mailto:privacy@fasttrack.co.uk); or you can phone 01865 297100.

**Contents  
**This privacy policy consists of the sections set out below. Please click on the section below for ease of navigation.

  * What we do
  * What personal data we need
  * Legal basis for processing your information
  * Sharing of information
  * International transfers
  * How long we keep your personal data for
  * Offer to remove personal data
  * Your rights in relation to your information
  * Cookies
  * Links to other websites
  * Modifications to this policy
  * Review of this policy

**What we do**  
Fast Track is a research and events firm that has created a network of private company directors through our league tables published in The Sunday Times.

In order to compile our league tables and arrange our networking dinners, it is necessary for us to collect and store basic personal data on company founders, directors and support staff. The majority of this data, although personal in nature, is publicly available on company websites and at Companies House.

Certain personal data that we collect may be obtained directly through telephone interviews and company visits or at our dinners. We are strongly committed to protecting this personal data and we take all reasonable steps to ensure it is stored securely.

**What personal data we need  
**Fast Track will only collect personal data, which does not include “special categories” of personal data as defined in Article 9 of the GDPR. The personal data that we collect and process can include:

  * Name, age, job title, shareholding;
  * Work address, switchboard telephone number;
  * Work or personal email address, work telephone number; and
  * For our alumni networking dinners, we also provide a booklet to guests and sponsors with: head-and-shoulders photo, short bio and hobbies, compiled with guests’ help and sent to them in advance for their review.

**We use the personal data we collect to:**

  * Research and write accurate profiles of our league table companies, published with The Sunday Times;
  * Foster relevant and appropriate relationships with the company directors; and
  * Invite (free-of-charge) directors to our events, enabling them to raise their profile, and utilise networking and business development opportunities.

Additionally, we may also collect and process information when you visit our website, including the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, geographical location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform.

**Legal basis for processing your information  
**We have a “legitimate interest” in collecting and storing your personal data for the purposes of compiling our league tables, organising company research visits and our networking dinners, and meeting our contractual obligations to our commercial sponsors (a list can be found on the front page of our website, [www.fasttrack.co.uk](https://www.fasttrack.co.uk/)).

We will not collect any personal data from you that we do not need in order to provide these services.

**Sharing of information**  
Your personal data will be processed by our staff in Oxford for the purposes of compiling our league tables, organising company research visits and our networking dinners, and meeting our contractual obligations to our sponsors.

Relying on “legitimate interest”, we may share your personal data with our sponsors for the purposes of effecting an introduction between the sponsor and your organisation at a senior level (i.e. B2B). Where the sponsor seeks to establish a relationship with you as an individual (i.e. B2C), we will gain your explicit consent before sharing your personal contact details, i.e. work or personal email address.

Your personal information may be transferred to third party service providers who process information on our behalf, including providers of information technology, identity management, website hosting and management, data analysis, data back-up, security and storage services. The third party providers may use their own third party subcontractors that have access to personal data.

**International transfers  
**We do not transfer your personal data to countries or territories outside the European Economic Area (the “ **EEA** “).

However, it is possible that third parties engaged by us in relation to the operation of the website might transfer your personal data to countries or territories outside the EEA. The third parties are:

  * _Google Analytics_
  * _Tsohost_
  * __WordPress__

If you require more on information on how these third parties use your personal data, then please visit:

  * _Google Analytics:_[ _google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/_](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)
  * _Tsohost:_[ _tsohost.com/legal/privacy-policy_](http://www.tsohost.com/legal/privacy-policy)
  * _WordPress: _automattic.com/privacy/__

**How long will we keep your personal data  
**We keep your personal data for as long as it is necessary in order to be able to consider your company for inclusion in our league tables and invite you to our networking awards and alumni dinners.

**Offer to remove personal data**  
If you do not wish to be invited to our networking dinners and do not want your personal data stored by us, then we will record this request and remove your personal data from our systems ­— please email [privacy@fasttrack.co.uk](mailto:privacy@fasttrack.co.uk)

**Your rights in relation to your information** **  
** You may have certain rights in relation to the personal information we hold about you. In particular, you may have a right to:

  * Request a copy of personal information we hold about you;
  * Ask that we update the personal information we hold about you, or correct such personal information that you think is incorrect or incomplete;
  * Ask that we delete personal information that we hold about you, or restrict the way in which we use such personal information;
  * Object to our processing of your personal information; and/or
  * Withdraw your consent to our processing of your personal information (to the extent such processing is based on consent and consent is the only permissible basis for processing).
  * If you would like to exercise these rights, please contact us by sending an email to privacy@fasttrack.co.uk or by one of the means set out in this privacy policy. We may charge for a request to access your information, if permitted by applicable law.

**Cookies  
**To make this website simpler, small data files are placed on your computer. These are known as cookies. Most big websites do this too. They improve things by:

  1. Remembering settings, so you don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever you visit a new page
  2. Remembering information you’ve given
  3. Measuring how you use the website so we can make sure it meets your needs

Our cookies aren’t used to identify you personally. They’re just here to make the site work better for you. Indeed, you can manage and/or delete these small files as you wish. We use Google Analytics to collect information about how people use this site. We do this to make sure it is meeting its users’ needs and to understand how we could do it better. Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here and what you click on. This information cannot be used to identify who you are. There are also cookies that store basic data on your interactions with WordPress, the CMS running this website. It is possible to switch off cookies by setting your browser preferences. Turning cookies off may result in a loss of functionality when using our website. To learn more about cookies and how to manage them, visit [AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

**Links to other websites**  
Our website contains links to other websites run by other organisations. This privacy policy applies only to our website‚ so we encourage you to read the privacy statements on the other websites you visit.

**Modifications** **  
** We may update this privacy policy at any time by publishing an updated version here. So you know when we make changes to this privacy policy, we will amend the revision date at the bottom of this page. The new modified or amended privacy policy will apply from that revision date. Therefore, we encourage you to review this privacy policy periodically to be informed about how we are protecting your information.

**Review of this policy  
**We keep this policy under regular review; it was last updated in May 2018.
